<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photography on TurtleTooth</title>
    <link>http://turtletooth.com/photography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photography on TurtleTooth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy 2015 - 2017, TurtleTooth Media.  All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://turtletooth.com/photography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>List of Emotions</title>
      <link>http://turtletooth.com/photography/emotions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 22:02:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://turtletooth.com/photography/emotions/</guid>
      <description>Choose from the list below and create a photo that conveys that emotion.     Negative and forceful  Anger Annoyance Contempt Disgust Irritation   Negative and not in control  Anxiety Embarrassment Fear Helplessness Lonely Powerlessness Worry   Negative thoughts  Doubt Envy Frustration Guilt Shame       Negative and passive  Boredom Despair Disappointment Hurt Sadness   Agitation  Stress Shock Tension   Positive and lively  Amusement Delight Elation Excitement Happiness Joy   Caring  Affection Empathy Friendliness Love        Positive thoughts  Courage Hope Pride Satisfaction Trust   Quiet positive  Calm Content Relaxed Relieved Serene   Reactive  Interest Politeness Surprised</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8th Grade Digital Media</title>
      <link>http://turtletooth.com/photography/8th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 21:59:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://turtletooth.com/photography/8th/</guid>
      <description>Digital Media Seminar Students in this class will work with digital cameras, video cameras, Photoshop Elements, iPhoto and iMovie to develop multimedia projects. Class activities will include a Claymation movie, silent movie, digital photography projects, a research project on American photographers, and a field trip with an emphasis on photography. Being familiar with digital photography and video would be helpful, but not a requirement. Students in the 2nd semester of this class will produce the 8th grade continuation video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6th Grade Photography</title>
      <link>http://turtletooth.com/photography/6th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 21:57:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://turtletooth.com/photography/6th/</guid>
      <description>Links Class Calendar
Class Software
Projects Coming soon&amp;hellip;
&amp;nbsp;
About the Class Intro to Digital Photography Students will learn to take great photos in this class as they explore the different types of photography and learn how to better use cameras. The class will help students understand the concepts of exposure, composition, and subject choice. Photo editing will also be covered as students learn to use Photoshop through a variety of creative projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Painted Animals</title>
      <link>http://turtletooth.com/photography/animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 21:46:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://turtletooth.com/photography/animals/</guid>
      <description>Click Here to Choose Your Animal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Shoe Project</title>
      <link>http://turtletooth.com/photography/shoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 21:44:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://turtletooth.com/photography/shoes/</guid>
      <description>Pick a type of shoe: High Tops
Nike Racers
Nike Air
More Nike
More Nike2 
More Nike3</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>